https://www.campaignbuttons-etc.com/information/3-privacy-policy.html

Campaign Buttons - Etc - Privacy Policy
HomePresidential Campaign ButtonsDonald Trump ButtonsHilary Clinton ButtonsBarack Obama ButtonsMitt Romney
ButtonsJohn McCain ButtonsJohn Kerry ButtonsGeorge W. Bush ButtonsAl Gore ButtonsBill Clinton ButtonsBob Dole ButtonsGeorge H.W. Bush ButtonsMichael Dukakis ButtonsRonald Reagan ButtonsWalter Mondale ButtonsJimmy Carter ButtonsGerald Ford ButtonsGeorge McGovern ButtonsRichard Nixon ButtonsHubert Humphrey ButtonsLyndon B. Johnson ButtonsBarry Goldwater ButtonsJohn F. Kennedy ButtonsRobert F. Kennedy ButtonsTed Kennedy ButtonsDwight Eisenhower ButtonsAdlai E. Stevenson ButtonsHarry S. Truman ButtonsThomas E. Dewey ButtonsWendell L. Willkie ButtonsFranklin D. Roosevelt ButtonsAlf Landon ButtonsHerbert Hoover ButtonsAl Smith ButtonsCalvin Coolidge Buttons John W Davis ButtonsWarren G. Harding ButtonsJames Cox ButtonsWoodrow Wilson ButtonsWilliam Howard Taft ButtonsAlton Parker ButtonsTheodore Roosevelt ButtonsWilliam McKinley Buttons3rd Party ButtonsPresidential Hopefuls ButtonsCharles Evans Hughes ButtonsWilliam Jennings Bryan ButtonsTed Kennedy ButtonsJeb Bush ButtonsMarco Rubio ButtonsTed Cruz ButtonsBernie Sanders ButtonsKamala Harris ButtonsElizabeth Warren ButtonsJoe Biden ButtonsBeto O’Rourke ButtonsPete Buttigieg Buttons2020
Hopefuls ButtonsNew ArrivalsLocalsEtcCause ButtonsLabor ButtonsFantasyPolitical PaperAdvertisingBlog
Currency
€
£
$
Shopping Cart
0 item(s) - $0.00
Your shopping cart is empty!
Welcome visitor you can login or create an account.
HomeWish List (0)My AccountShopping CartCheckout
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy:
Any customer placing an order with campaignbutton-etc.com can be assured any personal information provided will not be used for any purpose other than completing a sales transaction and shipping the item(s) to the purchaser.   We will not ever trade, sell, give away, bargain, barter or otherwise exchange this information with any other persons, parties, companies or entities.
campaignbutton-etc.com does not keep your credit card information on file.
campaignbutton-etc.com makes every attempt to treat your personal data the way we would expect to have ours treated.
campaignbutton-etc.com does collect the e-mail addresses of our customers.  Periodically campaignbutton-etc.com will use these e-mail addresses to notify our customers of new merchandise that has been posted and any upcoming sales. This e-mail list will never be sold, given away, bargained, bartered or otherwise exchanged with any other persons, parties, companies or entities.  Customers have the option of being removed from the list by entering “unsubscribe” in any e-mail that they may receive and returning it.
We use no cookies except the temporary ones utilized by our shopping cart which disappear after the purchase.
Copyright © 2016. All Rights Reserved.
